Sergey Zimakov

Backend Developer



Profile

Backend developer with 3+ years of experience, passion to learn and find effective and creative solutions.

Skills

Target oriented

Self-learner

Team Player

Organized

Highly motivated

Technical Skills

C#, NodeJS, SQL

API, .Net, Services

Git, CI/CD, Jira

Languages

Hebrew | Native

Russian | Native

English | Proficient

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sergey-zimakov https://sergeyzimakov.github.io/mycv/ https://github.com/SergeyZimakov 0544366021 zimakovs93@gmail.com

Experience

Backend Developer

April 2023 - Present

Galcon

Developing API servers and communication servers with C# and NodeJS

Significant improvement of load test capabilities by developing a new application that simulates running a big number of devices under different conditions.

Promoting and moving new features to test by making integration between Embedded side and Frontend.

Taking a part and responsibilities in most of the company's projects.

Full Stack Developer

August 2021 - March 2023

Minicy Catom

Developing energy control system with ASP.Net, system and data base characterization.

Improving the timing of energy reports and bills generating by fixing and creating complex procedures and functions in SQL.

Achieving system improvement by developing new effective features.

Developing Windows Services with C#.

Education

Full Stack Developer

March 2020 – April 2021

John Bryce - Haifa

Graduated with honours.

Programming Engineer

October 2018 - March 2020

ORT Braude – Karmiel

Termination of study due to personal reasons.

Electro-mechanical Junior Engineer

October 2015 - June 2017

ORT Braude - Karmiel

Graduated with honours.